asianscreens.com 2013-05-24

# AsianScreens - Privacy Policy

We at AsianScreens (UpNext) value your privacy. Please read this notice that explains our online information-gathering practices and how you can better protect against how various information is collected and used by other parties.

**We Collect Data About You that You Probably Don't Care if We Know**

Naturally, we will keep records of the name and email address you provide us if you sign up for our mailing list. And, of course, if you should order DVDs from our site, we will retain basic information about you such as your shipping and email addresses. We also may soak up non-personally identifying information when you visit our site such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g. Windows or Mac) and the domain name of your ISP (e.g. Comcast, AOL). We will not pass on any of the above information to third parties. However, should you click on a link on our site that takes you to a third party, please read their Privacy Policy regarding **_their use_** of any personal information **_you submit to them_** as it may be different from ours!

**Information About You Gathered by Third-Parties**

Our site may contain links to other sites that gather information and subsequently use it for purposes different from AsianScreens (UpNext). Visitors should consult privacy policies of such sites as our Privacy Policy does not extend to information you may submit to or is collected by third parties.

**Cookies**

Most of our web pages do make use of cookies, but this is really for the benefit of users. Cookies are text files placed in your computer's browser to store your preferences and provide records of what links you've previously visited on AsianScreens. Cookies cannot directly inform us of your e-mail address or any other personally identifying information. AsianScreens makes use of cookies to better comprehend visitor patterns, thus, enabling us to improve the content and features on the site.

**Security**

We do our utmost to ensure that proper electronic and managerial safeguards are in place to help maintain the security of all information shown on and sent to our site.

**Still Have Questions/Concerns about AsianScreens' (UpNext's) Privacy Policy?**

Should you have any questions or concerns about AsianScreens' Privacy Policy or the manner in which we implement it, please feel free to contact us via our contact us page..
